- Penny called us.
- Penny?
(Mrs Koothrappali:)She told us you're spending all our money
on your new girIfriend.
(Raj:)I just got her a couple of things.
(Raj:)She gives me things too.
Yeah, yeah. I'm a gynecologist.
l know exactly what she gives you.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)You need to find a nice Indian girl
from a good family.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)If you keep seeing this woman,
you're cut off.
What? You're gonna make me choose
between the woman I love...
(Raj:)...and the money
I have very strong feelings for?
(Dr Koothrappali:)It's up to you.
- Well, I choose love.
- Heh, you're an idiot.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Love doesn't last.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Well, he's going to find out eventually.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Think about it.